In the end, all the dreams I've made are the same
But of course, you and I always are the same
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
I'm going to go back to the place where I'm going to go
I'm so happy that I don't have to be with you
It's been a long time since I saw you.
I'm sure your smile will come true.
You and you and you
If you love me,
I'll be with you for a long time.
I'm sure I'll be able to remember you.
You scared me!
I realized everything
I wanted you to know this city will be great.
What do you even think about?
What I remember even after getting back this world.
But it wasn't.
The brothers too?
Are you pleased to have finally come back to the rest?
Bouncing
Let's play the tiles.
Jamming!
Jamming?
Jamming with a trick!
Jamming!
Jamming the tiles.
We can't stop like that.
Let's go to the mids!
Jamming!
Look!
It's hard to find a water tank.
Huh?
I always have water here.
I see.
I want to find a water tank here.
If you don't have water here, you'll get a water tank.
But why didn't you get a water tank?
It's strange.
I want to get a water tank.
Hey!
What's wrong?
It's so bad.
It's strange that we got a water tank.
Huh?
We got a water tank?
What are you doing here?
I don't know if you're watching.
Are you trying to get a water tank?
I'm trying to get a water tank.
Water tank?
This is a strange place.
Is this our chance to get a water tank?
Hmm.
If you don't want to go, you should go.
It's different, isn't it?
That's right.
It's a flower.
This is our main weapon.
Yeah, our main weapon too.
What are you looking for?
This tree is always in the middle of the mountain.
It's a very beautiful flower.
That's a beautiful flower.
Nika Nika.
That's not what I'm looking for.
Well, is that a game?
That's right.
If you do something like that, you won't be able to make it.
No.
There's nothing wrong with this tree.
It's all over the tree.
What's wrong?
When the tree had no flowers, the tree grew bigger.
The tree grew bigger.
That's why the tree grew bigger.
That's right.
It grew bigger.
I've been hurt so much.
Really?
When the sheath of this tree has no flowers,
the beautiful flower is everywhere.
The beautiful flower is everywhere.
How can the sheath of this tree grow up?
I'm sure there's no way to look for flowers.
There's nothing to worry about.
But I don't think we can do anything just for this three years.
I don't think we can do anything just for that.
I'm sure there's nothing to worry about.
Where should I go?
Anyway, I want to see the flowers.
But I don't think we can do anything just for this three years.
Maybe there's a lot of gold.
Let's find the flowers!
What are you doing?
No, that's not it.
Let's find the flowers!
There's nothing to worry about.
I've stopped.
But I don't think we can find them.
I'm sure there's nothing to worry about.
Let's find the flowers!
Ah…
Wait.
Is that something you can't do for yourself?
It's nothing I can't do for myself except this.
Did I get it?
That's it.
Just can't make it easy for the water to be taken.
Don't you have water?
If you have, you can buy this.
Oh, I see. The water was stopped.
That's why I took the water from the water.
The water was gone, so I don't have to drink water.
I don't have water, but I can't.
I don't know if the flowers in the tree are ripe.
I won't let you get away from me!
If you hear that,
I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry!
I'll get you out of here!
Let's go!
That's why I can't get out of here!
I'm not going to let you go!
I'll get you out of here!
Anyway, I don't know what's going on around here.
That's right.
Maka Maka!
Hey!
It's too much!
There's a lot of power in the Maka Maka, right?
It's a real archery pose.
Maka Maka!
Come back!
Let's go!
Maka Maka!
What's wrong?
It's water!
That's right, Maka Maka!
Maybe it's Maka Maka and Maka Maka.
I wonder if there's a way to get out of here.
I see!
Then, if you're going to get out of here,
you can get out of here with the water.
Yeah, probably.
Maka Maka doesn't do anything.
It's hot!
That's right.
Hey!
Is it still hot?
Ah!
Hey, you're back!
Are you alright?
Everyone, get up!
I'm going to die!
Hurry up!
The train's getting drunk!
You don't want to go out so soon?
I do.
I'm going to leave now!
Go!
Mom!
I'm sorry, Mom.
It's better...
Gotta eat!
Turn it over?
Shut up!
Wait!
I'm going to die!
I didn't do this!!
Wait!
Let's carry you!
I'm going to die!!
This is so funny!
I'm feeling so bad here.
Where did you go to that hat?
I do not know.
I do not know where in the water is.
What the...?
Huh?
I didn't know where it was before.
Oh, I see. The girl's heart is beating.
What should I do to get a doll?
Oh, no!
What?
Oh my god!
Mucamu Ka!
Where do we go?
Too good I've got it!
Oh my god!
I never got it first.
Really?
Shiggeyo!
This is the way the water flows, and the water has become lighter.
Then, if you want to get rid of this, you can go.
But how do you do it?
I don't think it's going to be easy.
It's okay if it's in the back yard.
Back yard?
Mark, Mark, Mark.
Mark, Mark, Mark, Mark, Mark, Mark!
Okay, then let us clean number one at a safe place.
Ah, Mark!
Mark...
Oh no. Where'd the real thing get along with it?
It was a volatile place. If it's a little further, there's only one single hole.
All right, I'll take care of it.
Take care of everyone!
Hey, you too!
Good luck!
Let's go!
Did I save the rest?
How about this?
I don't think it'll be a bad luck!
Yeah, it'll be like this at once.
I'll have to take care of it.
What are you doing?
Hey!
Hurry up!
It's not a game, so...
What's going on?
Hey, what's going on?
Hurry up!
Stop it!
What are you doing?
What's going on?
Stop it!
Hey!
What are you talking about?
Stop it!
If you don't do this, you won't be able to do it.
Maybe you're trying to do something?
I think so too.
Is there something in the map?
Hey, you!
What are you talking about?
Tell me!
What's going on?
Huh?
I see.
It's because there's a lot of people around here.
There's a lot of people around here.
I see.
Oh, it's coming out!
This is the center of Bakuyaku.
Let's go!
If you don't do this, you'll be able to do it.
Don't go wrong.
Stop it!
It's coming out!
I did it!
There's a lot of people around here.
I see.
It's coming out!
Stop it!
Look, it's coming out!
I thought water was too strong.
I did it!
And I was so beautiful!
I don't know!
Beautiful flower, huh?
Yeah, I'm so happy to be here.
So beautiful!
I'm so happy to be here!
I see!
Look at me!
I heard this!
I heard the sound of flowers blooming in the flowers.
Ah, I see.
Is it different from what I saw?
Hey, everyone.
I'm so happy to be here.
Let's play the same between us.
Huh?
That's fine.
Ha ha!
This isn't good!
Ha!
I see!
Oh no!
yeah, yeah, yeah, uh-oh,
balladize
来て,来て,来て
来て,来て
誰も 誰も 泣かまだよ
I'm glad that I was able to walk with you
走り方いてよ
I'm walking
乗り乗り
I always walk
I'm walking
it was with an Indian taste
What a great idea!
For us, it doesn't deserve
A heart-shaped ending
The first day of the day
The man in the middle of the university was not sleeping,
but his father was saved.
He was a little bit scared.
I want to give him something,
but I wonder if he can be a father with a pet shop.
Next time, I'll be a friend of the Kodamuka Paradais.
I'll be a friend of the Kodamuka Paradais.
I'll be looking forward to it!
Thank you for watching.